Guide to the New York State College of Human Ecology. Research Office records, 1947-2007
New York State College of Human Ecology. Research Office records, 1947-2007
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State College of Human Ecology. Research Office records, 1947-2007.
23-7-2829
New York State College of Human Ecology. Research Office.
12.5 cubic ft.
Publications, correspondence, reports, financial documents.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Reports, correspondence, and other records pertaining to the College's research, grant distribution, academic studies, funding, and programs.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Reports, correspondence, and other records pertaining to the College's research, grant distribution, academic studies, funding, and programs.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State College of Human Ecology.
Subjects:
Human ecology--Research.; Home economics--Research.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIALS
Includes collection #23-07-1063.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Committees
Box 2
A. College Research Committee
B. College Grants Committee
Series II. Grant Material
Boxes 1, 2, 4, 5, 7, 9
Series III. Publications
Boxes 3, 4, 5, 7
A. NY Food and Life Science Quarterly
B. Research Notes
C. Theses
D. Particulars
Series IV. Manuals
Box 4
Series V. Reports
Boxes 2, 3, 7
A. Annual
B. Blackwell, 1966
C. Final Report to the President
D. Project
E. Welfare Study, 1966-1970
Series VI. Subjects Files
Box 2
Series VII. Research Files
Boxes 1-5, 7, 8
Series VIII. Faculty Research Reports
Box 6
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Committees
  - College Research Committee
    - Reorganization and Name Change (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - College Name Change (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Memoranda and Voting, Faculty Response (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Memoranda and Voting, Reorganization (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Blackwell Reports, Name Change (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Undergraduates in the College of Home Economics (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - John Harding Project Statements, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Research Committee, 1946-1955 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - College Grants Committee
    - Research, John Harding, 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Graduate Student Funding, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - College Grants Committee Meeting Minutes, 1974-1978, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 9A)
    - College Grants Committee Annual Reports, 1975-1976, 1978-1979, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 9B)
      (the 1980-1981 report is in collection 23-2-2817, box 1)
- Series II. Grant Material
  - College Grant Policy History (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Abstracts from College Grants, 1978-1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - College Grants Survey, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Grant Applications, Research, Mary Morrison (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Research Grants, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Research Grants and Contracts, Annual Reports, 1978-1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Research Grants and Contracts, Annual Reports, 1982-1985 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Research Grants and Contracts, Annual Reports, 1986-1989 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Research Grants and Contracts, Annual Reports, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Research Grants and Contracts, Annual Reports, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Research Grants and Contracts, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Research Grants, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Research Grants, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Research Grants, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Grants to Human Ecology Faculty, 1994-07-1995-06, 1995-07-1996-06 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Grants to Human Ecology Faculty, 1996-07-1997-06, 1997-07-1998-06 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Grants to Human Ecology Faculty, 1998-07-1999-06, 1999-07-2000-06 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Grants to Human Ecology Faculty, 2000-07-2001-06, 2001-07-2002-06 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Grants to Human Ecology Faculty, 2002-07-2003-06, 2003-07-2004-06, 2004-07-2005-06 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - College Grants for Faculty Seed and Innovation Projects, 1989-2006 (Box 9, Folder 5a)
  - Grants to Human Ecology Faculty, 2005-07-2006-06 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Series III. Publications
  - New York Food and Life Science Quarterly
    - Copy of New York's Food and Life Sciences Quarterly (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Research Notes
    - Research Notes - supplements 1-14, 1979-01-1979-12 (Box 3)
    - Research Notes - supplements 1-14, 1980-01-1980-12 (Box 3)
    - Research Notes and supplements, 1980 (Box 3)
    - Research Notes, 1982-01-1995-05 (Box 3)
  - Theses
    - Research in Home Economics and Home Economics Education, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1924-1940 (Box 3)
    - Research on Home Economics an the Land-Grant Institutions Vol. I, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1927-1946 (Box 3)
    - Research in Home Economics at the Land-Grant Institutions Vol. II, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1940-1941, 1951-1952 (Box 3)
    - Notes on Graduate Studies and Research in Home Economics, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1940-1946 (Box 3)
    - Completed Theses in Home Economics and Related Fields in Colleges and Universities of the United States, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1947-1953 (Box 3)
    - Research in Home Economics at the Land-Grant Institutions, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1937-1938 (Box 3)
  - "Particulars", 1990-05-1995-05 (Box 7, Folder 26 (volumes 17-22))
- Series IV. Manuals
  - Faculty Research Manuals, 1962, 1969, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Research Manuals, 1981, 1983, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Research Manuals, 1987, 1989, 1991, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Series V. Reports
  - Annual
    - Annual Reports, 1981, 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - University Annual Reports for Research, 1949-1954 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - University Annual Reports for Research, 1954-1958 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - University Annual Reports for Research, 1959-1960 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - University Annual Reports for Research, 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - University Annual Reports for Research, 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Blackwell
    - Blackwell Reports, Name Change, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Final Report to the President
    - Final Report to President, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Project
    - Project Reports, 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Welfare Study, 1966-1970
    - Welfare Study, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Welfare Study, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Welfare Study (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Series VI. Subject Files
  - Reorganization and Name Change (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - College Name Change (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Voting, Faculty Response (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Voting, Reorganization (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Undergraduates in the College of Home Economics (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Student Funding (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Long Term Care Administrators, Miriam Dolson (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Rent Subsidy Program, Mary Langford (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - IRGOP (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Research Funding (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Instruction and Department Research (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Faculty Memoranda, Name Change (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Faculty Committees (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Status of Textiles and Clothing, Recommendations (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Budget, 1972 College of Human Ecology (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Series VII. Research Files
  - Home Economics Related Projects in CRIS, 1971-10 (Box 4, Folder 9A)
  - Overhead Research Awards, 1973-11-1981-02 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Research, John Harding (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Research, John Harding (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Research, W. Brittain (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Research into Child Development, Ginsburg (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Research, Aletha Stein (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Research, Aletha Stein (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Research, Child Development (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Research, Child Development (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Research Funding (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Research, Education in Ghana (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Memoranda concerning Research, 1980-1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Research Projects and Related Publications done in the Departments-College of Home Economics (lists), 1962-1969 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Scope and Focus of Research Activities at the College of Human Ecology by Richard Chapman, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Research stats, 1990-1999 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Summary of Research for the Departments in the College of Human Ecology, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - College of Human Ecology - Research Accomplishments, 1980-1999 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - College of Human Ecology - Research Accomplishments, 1980-1999 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Research - Financial Information, 1980-1999 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Research Issues, 1947-1971 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Faculty - Overview of Research, 1990-1999 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Research - Summaries of what is done in departments, and correspondence, 1950-1969 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Research - Utilization of Salvaged Meat Fats - Fenton, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Space for Research - Correspondence, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Progress Reports and Project Statements, 1962-1965 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Progress Reports and Project Statements, 1950-1969 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Marketing Research - Correpondence, 1960-1969 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Consumers Union of U.S. - Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Outside Requests for Research Reports, 1940-1959 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Historical Review of Research in the College of Home Economics, 1925-1937 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Research Proposals, 1940-1949 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Research Proposals, 1945-1951 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Research Proposals, 1951-1953 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Research Proposals, 1955-1961 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Research Proposal - A Study of the Attitudes of Rural Mothers Toward the Use of Authority with Children of Preschool Age, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Philco, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Potato Research, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Yale Study, 1946-1949 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Work Measurement in Institutional Food Production and Service - I.M. (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Resources for Research, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Research Resumes
    - Ashdown, Susan, 1992, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Avery, Robert, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Avery, Rosemary, 1999, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Burkhauser, Richard, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Butler, John (J.S.), 2000 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Canfield, Richard, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Casasola, Marianella, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Ceci, Stephen, 1996, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Chi, Peter, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Chu, C.C., 1997 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Cochran, Moncrieff, 1990, 1995, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Danko, Sheila, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Elliott, John (Jack), 1999 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Eshelman, Paul, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Evans, Gary, 1992, 1993, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Frongillo, Edward (Jr.), 1998 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Govindaraj, Muthu, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Grazier, Kyle, 1993, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Greene, Katrina, 1996, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Hahn, Alan, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Hamilton, Stephen, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Haugaard, Jeffrey, 1990, 1992, 1996, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Hedge, Alan, 1991, 1996, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Hogarth, Jeanne, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Jennings, Jan, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Kenkel, Donald, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Kuder, John, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Laquatra Jr., Joseph, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Lemley, Ann, 1999, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Lenzenweger, Mark, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Lillard, Dean, 1992, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Loker, Suzanne, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Mathios, Alan, 1992, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Maxwell, Lorraine, 1995, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Moen, Phyllis, 1995, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Mueller, Jeanne, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Netravali, Anil, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Obendorf, S. Kay, 1992, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Ochs, Mary, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Parrot, Andrea, 1991, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Pollak, Patricia, 1991, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Potts, Marion, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Rasmussen, Kathleen, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Rendall, Michael, 1993, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Ricciuti, Henry, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Rodriguez, Eunice, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Schultz, Jennifer, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Shapiro, Constance, 1989, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Street, Lloyd, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Suci, George, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Tennyson, Sharon, 1998, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Trochim, William, 1991, 1996, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Walston, Stephen, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Wang, Qi, 2000, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Watkins, Susan, 1997, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Wethington, Elaine, 1993, 1994, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Zorn, Peter, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 57)
- Series VIII. Faculty Research Reports
  - Allen, Josephine - Families, Gender, Empowerment, Social Welfare Policy, and the Political Economy of Urban and Rural Communities Domestically and Globally, HSS, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Avery, Robert- Savings and Wealth: Evidence from the 1983 and 1096 Survey of Consumer Finances, CEH, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Avery, Rosemary - Special Needs Adoption in New York State, PAM, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Avery, Rosemary - Public Agency Adoption in New York State, CEH, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Avery, Rosemary and Mathios, Alan - Food and Nutrition Messages Communicated Through Prime-Time Television, CEH, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Barr, Donald - Empowerment and Family Support, HSS, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Battistella, Roger - Health Administration, HSS, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Battistella, Roger - Health Policy Studies, HSS, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Becker, Franklin - Managing Environmental Change, DEA, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Becker, Franklin and Sims, William - Development of a Decision Model for Evaluating the Cost Performance of University Research Laboratory Facilities, DEA, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Becker, Franklin and Sims, William - The Ecology of Remote Collaborative Work, DEA, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Beckman, Ronald - Toward a Theory of Benign Design, DEA, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Brooks, Richard - Perceptions of Fairness in the American Legal System, PAM, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Brumburg, Joan - A Social and Cultural History of Anorexia Nervosa, HDFS, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Brumberg, Joan - Social and Cultural History of Female Adolescents, 1900-1900, HDFS, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Brumberg, Joan - Social and Cultural History of Female Adolescence, 1800-1900, HDFS, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Bryant, W. Keith - Economics and the Family, PAM, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Buchanan, R - Patient Characteristics in Nursing Homes: Differences Between Medicaid Recipient Receiving Skilled Care and Intermediate Care, HSS, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Burchfield, David - The Effects of Managed Care on Non-managed Care Patients, PAM, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Canfield, Richard - NIMH Postdoctoral Fellow - Infant Visual Anticipation and Number Perception, HDFS, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Ceci, Brofenbrenner, Cornelius - Activites and Mentors: An Experiment in Building Teenage Competence, HDFS, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Ceci, Stephen - Contextual Constraints on Cognitive Competence, HDFS, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Chi, Peter - What are the Prospects for the Minority Elderly in the United States?, CEH, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Chu, C.C. - A New Radiation Sterilization Method for Orthopedic Polymeric Implants, TXA, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Chu, C.C. - Design and Testing of Textile Materials for Medical/Surgical Use, TXA, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Chu, C.C. - Surface Modification of Absorbable Suture Materials, TXA, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Cochran, Moncrieff - Economic Stress, Social Support, and the School-Aged Child, HDFS, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Condry, John - Human Development and Television Research Lab, HDFS, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Cornelius, Steven - Middle-Age Adults Beliefs about Mid-Life Development, HDFS, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Crawford, Catherine - A Pilot Study of the Patterns of Dating Behavior Within a Sample Undergraduate Population, HSS, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Danko, Sheila - Relationships of the Physical Environment to Creative Problem-Solving and Design Process (old: Ongoing Research into Designers Methods and Design Process), DEA, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Danko, Sheila - A Comparison of the Design Process and Methods Used by the Range of Professionals Practicing Interior Design, DEA, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Depue, Richard - Assessment of Ocular Norepinephrine, HDFS, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - DeWeese, Gail - Female-Headed Household: The Impact of Family Structure on Household Expenditures for Clothing, TXA, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Doris, John and Eckenrode, John - Child Abuse and Neglect Research, HDFS, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Doris, John and Eckenrode, John - National Data Archives, FLDC, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Eckenrode, John - Statewide Teamwork for Abused Runaways (STAR), HDFS, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Eckenrode, John - Consortium for Research Involving Stress Processes, HDFS, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Eckenrode, John - Consortium for Research Involving Stress Processes, HDFS, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Eckenrode, John - Consortium for Research Involving Stress Processes, FLDC, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Eckenrode, John - Child Abuse Prevention Network, FLDC, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Eckenrode, John and Doris, John - Toxicology Testing of Neonates as an Indicator of Risk for Child Abuse, FLDC, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Eshelman, Paul - Fit Between the Computer and the User, DEA, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Eshelman, Paul - Fit Between the Computer and the User, DEA, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Eshelman, Paul - Fit Between the Computer and the User, DEA, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Evans, Gary - Crowding and Human Behavior, DEA, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Evans, Gary - Methodological Issues in Human-Environment Relations, DEA, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Ford, John - Access to Health Care for Uninsured and Underinsured Consumers, HSS, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Ford, John - The Role of Business and Industry in Controlling Health Care Costs, HSS, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Garbarino, James - Children's Rights and Child Protection: A North-South Collaboration, FLDC, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Garbarino, James - Developing a Training Package to Support the Use of Childhood Violence, FLDC, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Gerner, Jennifer and Zorn, Peter - An Analysis of Vatiation in Food Consumption Across Household Types and Over Time, CEH, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Gibson, Kathleen - Computer Simulation and its Effectiveness in Design Education, DEA, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Govindaraj, Muthu - Nathematical Modeling of Fabric Drape, TXA, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Govindaraj, Muthu - Application of Robots in Garment Assembly, TXA, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Greene, Jennifer - Evaluation of Parenting Skills Workshop Series, PAM, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Greene, Jennifer - Strengthening the Theory and Practices of Alternative Approaches to Social Program Evaluation, HSS, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Hamilton, Stephen - Youth Development in Community Settings, HDFS, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Hamilton, Stephen - Youth Apprenticeship, HDFS, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Haugaard, Jeffrey - Children's Definitions of the Truth, HDFS, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Hazan, Cindy - Processes of Attachment Formation and Transfer, HDFS, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Hazan, Cindy - Measurement and Investigation of Adult Attachment Phenomena, HDFS, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Heck, Ramona,and Trzcinski, Eileen - Employment Diversification and Entrepreneurial Opportunites within Rural Areas, CEH, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Hedge, Alan - Effects of Office Lighting on Comfort and Health, DEA, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Henderson, Charles - Methods and Analyses in the Ecology of Human Development, HDFS, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Hester, Susan - Resource Diversification Among the Working Poor: A Study of Women in Apparel Manufacturing (under S. Feldman, Rural Sociology), TXA, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Jacobsen, Linda - Determinants of Delayed Childbearing in the United States: A Longitudinal Analysis, CEH, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Jennings, Jan - The Practical Architect; or, Guide to Carpentry and Building, CEH, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Jennings, Jan - The Language of Internal Arrangement: Advice and Patterns,, DEA, 1800-1900 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Jirousek, Charlotte - Islamic Influences in Western Dress, TXA, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Kabcenell, Andrea - Technical Assistance and Direction for Improving the Quality of Hospital Care, HSS, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Kabcenell, Andrea - Health Services Demonstration and Research, HSS, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Kenkel, Donald - Eonomic Incentives for Worksite Alcohol Abuse Services, CEH, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Key, Rosemary (Avery) - Managerial Decision-Making Related to Activity Sequencing in Household Production, CEH, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Koslowski, Barbara - Reasoning About Causal Explanations, HDFS, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Kuder, John - Evaluation of UHS System Case Management, HSS, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Kutty, Nandinee - Research on the United States Housing Sector Using American Housing Survey Data, CEH, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Lazar Irving - Family Structure and Parent-Child Relationships, CEH, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Lee, Lee - Chinese Immigrant Children: Stress and Coping, HDFS, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Lemley, Ann - Electrochemical Removal of Pesticides from Water, TXA, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Lemley, Ann - Electrochemical Treatment of Pesticide Wastewater, TXA, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Lenzenweger, Mark - Sustained Attention, Affective Processes, and Psychopathology in Schizotypic Individuals, HDFS, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Lust, Barbara - Naturalistic and Experimental Study of First Language Acquisition, HDFS, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Maxwell, Lorraine - Preschool Classroom Environments and the Effects on Normal and Special Education Children, DEA, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Maynes, E. Scott - The Frontiers of Consumer Economics, CEH, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - McClintock, Charles - Managing Information for Program Development, HSS, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - McClintock, Charles - Research and Practitioner Knowledge About Organizational Collaboration, PAM, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Moen, Phyllis - Social Change and the Life Course: East and West, HDFS, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Moen, Phyllis - Women's Roles and Health Over the Life Course, HDFS, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Moen, Phyllis and Dempster-McClain, D. - Women's Roles and Well-Being: A Two Generation Study, HDFS, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Moen, Phyllis and Dempster-McClain, D. - Women's Roles and Well-Being: A Two Generation Study, HDFS, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Mont, Daniel - The Impact of Women's Careers on Family Migration, CEH, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Mueller, B. Jeanne - Family and Community Life of the Aged in Rural Cooperative Settlements, HSS, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Netravali, Anil - Geosynthetic Materials, HDFS, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Netravali, Anil - A Study of Co60 Gamma Radiation on Epoxy/Graphite Interface, TXA, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Obendorf, S. Kay - Polymer Resist Systems for Electron Beam Lithography, DEA, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Obendorf, S. Kay - Analysis of the Distribution of Residual Soils to Define Soil/Fabric/Formulation Characteristics that Limit Detergency, TXA, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Peters, H. Elizabeth - Child Support, Child Care, and Child Well-Being, CEH, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 2)